<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arifin</string>
    <string name="universitas_hamzanwadi">Hamzanwadi University</string>
    <string name="wisata_air_terjun">Waterfall Tours</string>
    <string name="wisata_pantai">Beach Tours</string>
    <string name="wisata_pegunungan">Hiking Tours</string>
    <string name="wisata_religi">Religious Tours</string>
    <string name="daftar_ras_hewan">Race tour list</string>
    <string name="wisata_judul">tourism</string>
    <string name="jenis_wisata">Travel types</string>
    <string name="asal">origin</string>
    <string name="deskripsi">Description</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
    <string name="jenis_row">Type</string>
    <string name="asal_row">Origin</string>
    <string name="nama_airterjun">Two levels of beauty in the vicinity of gile</string>
    <string name="lokasi">The village of senaru</string>
    <string name="airterjun">Being in the famous village of senaru, you have to walk through the forest and river to reach the sensation of gile. But don\'t worry, the ride will be exciting and pleasant because of the cool weather in the mountains that you will enjoy</string>
    <string name="nama">The twins and the tall; Tiu teja and tiu sekeper</string>
    <string name="santong">Santong village, sub-district of heaven, lombok northern district.</string>
    <string name="desc2air">Teja in the local language means rainbow. You can find this rainbow at the bottom of the falls when sunlight can reach it. Tiu teja is also a twin waterfall with two streams falling side by side. The stream was quite rapid, the water was clear and very cold.</string>
    <string name="nama3">Majestic natural theater in tiu kelep</string>
    <string name="lokasi3">Sena ru village, parrot district, lombok northern district.</string>
    <string name="desc3">So, basically it has two levels. The main waterfall with the largest stream falls directly from the highest level. Meanwhile, the lower level is a smaller range of flow in the cliff. They all fell into the same pool.</string>
    <string name="nama4">Sweet, sweet orange falls</string>
    <string name="lokasi4">Yellow flower village, brush-district, east lombok district</string>
    <string name="desc4">Still at the foot of mount rinjani, the sweet orange falls are on the east side of this volcanic slope. The falls still make up mount rinjani national park. It is believed that the falls were first discovered by communities about the mid-1980\'s.</string>
    <string name="nama5">Blue pool of Maya umar falls</string>
    <string name="lok5">Village of bilok petung, boong district, lombok district east.</string>
    <string name="desc5">The falls flow into a large natural pool. The water varies in color from toska green to sky blue. This pond is carved into a giant rock, so you\'ll remember the legends of fairies who descend on earth.</string>
    <string name="nama6">The unveiling cape bloam exoticism</string>
    <string name="lok6">Street. Beloam coast, cape ringgit, jerowaru, oh, lombok east.</string>
    <string name="desc6">The east lombok has many beautiful beaches, especially in the southeast. Although roads have been heavily paved in recent years, access to some beaches in the region is still very difficult. One of the beaches where it is mandatory to visit in lombok east is cape bloam (sometimes also called cape beloam).</string>
    <string name="nama7">Crazy kondo, nice sand island</string>
    <string name="loc7">Labuhan sambelias. East lombok:</string>
    <string name="desc7">Gili kondo is one of the small island groups located in the pedestal strait. This means that the islands are between lombok and summits. Like most of the islets around lombok, gili kondo is also incredibly exotic</string>
    <string name="name8">Cape ringgit, an untouched beauty</string>
    <string name="loc8">Street. Lingkok siwaq, oh, jerowaru, lombok district east</string>
    <string name="desc8">\"At the southeast corner of lombok, cape ringgit is a very unusual beach. You can find a variety of different beauties here. The first is a high cliff that collides directly with the blue sea.</string>
    <string name="name9">Burning pink sand on the coast of tangsi</string>
    <string name="loc9">Oh village, jerowaru district, lombok district east</string>
    <string name="desc9">Not many beaches in the world have pink sand, A.K.A. pink, but Indonesia has some, one in lombok. Tangsi beach on jerowaru has a brilliant natural pink hue. This color is possible because it combines white sand with dead red coral. Here you can see an unrivaled hue. It starts in white, pink sand, into the toska sea, into dark blue in the depths.</string>
    <string name="name10">\"Crossing into savana gili sunut\"</string>
    <string name="loc10">Temeak village, lokong village, jerowaru district, lombok east</string>
    <string name="desc10">Still at oh, jerowaru, you can also find an island that is very unusual; Gili sunut. The first line of crazy is its\' flexible \'access</string>
    <string name="name11">\"The hill of gashes\"</string>
    <string name="loc11">East lombok semis</string>
    <string name="desc11">Amazing view of lombok and rinjani from altitude: the hill of gastric ate</string>
    <string name="loc12">\"Hometown of gumise, gerong, west lombok\"</string>
    <string name="desc12">To reach this hill, we need an hour\'s drive from the city of mataram. Situated in the village of gumise, gerung, lombok west makes visitors to this hill most of the region of lombok west and mataram</string>
    <string name="name13">Preservation hill</string>
    <string name="loc13">Village tawun, district sekotong, lombok west</string>
    <string name="desc13">\"Located in the village of tawun, sekotong district, west lombok, the hill can be covered by motorized vehicles to reach the summit. From the top of the hill you can see the seaside of the sekotong region and some small islands.\"</string>
    <string name="name14">Hill of the sapling</string>
    <string name="loc14">\"Village of sembalun\"</string>
    <string name="desc14">In the village of sembalun too, the hills of the young are higher than the hills of gasket. If the hill of gasmeal takes two hours, the virgin\'s hill can be 3 hours.</string>
    <string name="name15">Nanggi of the sapling</string>
    <string name="loc15">Village of sembalun</string>
    <string name="desc15">The hills of gi are also located in the village of sembalun, in the east of lombok. Compared to the rice hills and the saplings, the eatula can be the highest on the hill line in the lombok this article. To get to the top of the noodle lunch hill, you have to walk soft trekking for about 4 hours</string>
    <string name="nmae16">1.  The tomb is in the ancient bayan baleq mosque</string>
    <string name="loc16">Parrot village, parrot district, lombok northern district</string>
    <string name="desc16">The mosque in machal is one of the buildings that bear silent witness to islamic development in the lombok soil. This ancient bayan balek mosque contains a number of tombs, one of which is the abdul rozak\'s grave and is thought to be the one spreading Islam in lombok.</string>
    <string name="name17">\"The tomb in the real guardian\"</string>
    <string name="loc17">\"West lombok.\"</string>
    <string name="desc17">In the opinion of the local community, the real guardian is one of the legendary trustees of the lombok west area. The real guardian cemetery is frequented daily by pilgrims, especially on wednesdays. The existence of a real guardian tomb is believed to solve a wide range of people\'s problems.</string>
    <string name="name18">\"The tomb of muhammad zaiduddin abdul madmosque and almagfurlah tomb\"</string>
    <string name="loc18">Pancor, east lombok selong</string>
    <string name="desc18">\"Muhamad zaiduddin a. m and almagfurlah used to be the clerics who spread Islam on the lombok soil. And not only that, they are courageous people because they continue to fight for the spread of Islam in the face of Indonesia\'s efforts because of its colonization of Japan.\"</string>
    <string name="name19">To know the history of the southern kingdom in the southern tomb</string>
    <string name="loc19">Suwela district, east lombok district,</string>
    <string name="desc19">As its name suggests, the existence of the viscera tomb was closely related to the southern kingdom. The celaparang kingdom was one of the Hindu kingdoms of Indonesia, whose victories ranged from the 13th to the 16th century.</string>
    <string name="name20">Pilgrimage to the tomb of loang baloq lombok</string>
    <string name="loc20">Mataram</string>
    <string name="desc20">In sasak, the word loang baloq has the sense of a hollow banyan tree. This is because in the burial area of loang baloq, there is a berkian tree that is hundreds of years old</string>
    <string name="pegunungan">Mountains</string>
    <string name="pantai">Beach</string>
    <string name="religi">released</string>
    <string name="air">waterfall</string>
    <string name="pgn">Mountains</string>
    <string name="pti">Beach</string>
    <string name="rlg">released</string>
    <string name="terjun">waterfall</string>
    <string name="name1_2">Rock of beauty</string>
    <string name="nama1">Name</string>
    <string name="nim">NIM</string>
    <string name="prodi">Major</string>
    <string name="kelas">Class</string>
    <string name="hobi">Hobby</string>
    <string name="teknik_informatika">Information Enginee</string>
    <string name="teknik_informatika_b">Information Enginee-B</string>
    <string name="programming">Programming</string>
</resources>